let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Approximately,how long does it take for the Sun's light to reach earth?",
    answer: "8 Minutes",
    options: [
      "6 Minutes",
      "8 Seconds",
      "8 Hours",
      "8 Minutes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many centimeters are in 5 Kilometers?",
    answer: "5,00,000 cm",
    options: [
      "500 cm",
      "5,00,000 cm",
      "50,000 cm",
      "5,000 cm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many bones are in a human body?",
    answer: "206",
    options: [
      "226",
      "408",
      "106",
      "206"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The speed of your net access is defined in terms of...",
    answer: "Kbps",
    options: [
      "RAM",
      "MHz",
      "Kbps",
      "Megabytes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A zinc diffusion process is called",
    answer: "sherardizing",
    options: [
      "galvanising",
      "anodising",
      "	parkerising",
      "sherardizing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How Many Sides are there in a Decagon?",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Computers calculate numbers in what mode?",
    answer: "Binary",
    options: [
      "Decimal",
      "Octal",
      "Binary",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A half-moon protractor is divided into how many degrees",
    answer: "180",
    options: [
      "360",
      "180",
      "270",
      "310"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The friction experienced by a body, when in motion, is known as",
    answer: "dynamic friction",
    options: [
      "rolling friction",
      "dynamic friction",
      "limiting friction",
      "static friction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How Many Months Make a Century?",
    answer: "1200",
    options: [
      "12",
      "120",
      "1200",
      "12000"
    ]
  },


];